[
  {
    "question": "1 + 7",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "25 - 41",
    "answer": -16
  },
  {
    "question": "41 - 23 + 39",
    "answer": 57
  },
  {
    "question": "34 * 35 / 100",
    "answer": 11.9
  },
  {
    "question": "3 powerof 8",
    "answer": 6561.0
  },
  {
    "question": "10 factorial",
    "answer": 3628800
  },
  {
    "question": "81 * 21 + 23 - 40",
    "answer": 1684
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 5",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 2 - 4 / 42",
    "answer": 2.9047619047619047
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 2 - 4 / 4",
    "answer": 2.0
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 2 - 4 / 4",
    "answer": 2.0
  }
]